>> 演讲者 1: 我们一直在讨论编译阶段的功能，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: We've been talking about
functions in the compilation phase,
将其标识添加为外层作用域中的彩色大理石。
adding their identifier as a colored
marble in the enclosing scope.
在这个例子中，我们有一个功能老师，
In this example,
we have a function teacher on line one,
什么颜色的大理石老师
what color marble is teacher gonna be?
>> 扬声器 2: 红色。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Red.
>> 扬声器 1: 红色，好的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Red, okay.
但让我们看第三行，因为线看起来有点不同。
But let's look at line three because
line looks a little bit different.
第三行可能看起来更像一些函数
And line three might look a little bit
more like some of the functions that
你见过更常见的
you've seen more commonly.
看到旧的学校功能装饰也许有点不太常见
It's maybe a little less common to see
the old school function decoration,
虽然我更喜欢功能装饰只是为了记录
although I strongly prefer function
decorations just for the record.
但现在大多数人都喜欢声明变量和
But most people seem to like these
days to declare variables and
将函数分配给它们，通常它们甚至使用常量而不是变量。
assign functions to them and usually they
even use a constant instead of a var.
这看起来有点像你最近看到的。
So that might look a little bit
like what you've seen recently.
所以在那里发生了什么
So what's happening there and
跟第一个的情况有什么不同吗
is it any different than what's
happening with line one?
嗯，记住，编译时发生的事有区别
Well, remember, there is a difference
between what can happen at compile time
以及执行时可能发生的情况。
and what can happen at execution time.
因此，我们知道将会创建名为 myTeacher 的标识，并且
So, we do know that an identifier called
myTeacher is going to be created and
那是什么颜色的大理石
what color marble is it gonna be?
>> 扬声器 2: 红色。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Red.
>> 扬声器 1: 将是红色的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: It's gonna be red.
我们知道那里有个叫阳极老师的功能，所以
We do know that there's a function
called anotherTeacher there, so
我们至少得为它创造一个桶
we need to create a bucket for
it at least.
我们得做个蓝色的水桶
We need to make a blue bucket.
但是因为那个功能不是一个宣言，
But because that function
is not a declaration,
我们不会以同样的方式处理它的大理石颜色
we're not gonna handle its
marble color in the same way.
这里的关键区别在于 " 老师 " 的标识符
The key difference here is that
the anotherTeacher identifier,
就在 3 号线上那个标识将以大理石的身份结束
the one right here on line three, that
identifier is going to end up as a marble
但它会是一个不同颜色的大理石
at compile time but it's gonna be a
different colored marble than you expect.
不是红色的大理石是蓝色的大理石
It's not a red marble, it's a blue marble.
所以这里有一个关键的区别。
So there is a key difference here.
这称为函数表达式，与第一行的函数表达式相反，
This is called a function expression
as opposed to what line one is,
称为函数声明。
is called a function declaration.
还有一个关键的差异，我们会在整个过程中看到更多的
And one of the key differences, and
we'll see more throughout the course but
函数声明和函数声明之间的键差异之一
one of the key differences
between function declarations and
函数表达式，是函数声明及其名称，
function expressions, is that
function declarations and their name,
他们把大理石附在封闭的范围内，所以我们在第一条线上制作了一个红色的大理石
they attach their marble to the enclosing
scope, so we make a red marble on line one
而函数表达式会将其大理石添加到自己的作用域中。
whereas function expressions will
add their marble to their own scope.
>> 扬声器 1: 蓝色的范围是蓝色大理石another教师节结束的地方。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: So the blue scope is where
the blue marble anotherTeacher ends up.
>> 扬声器 1: 这就是第 4 行的原因，我们可以在 " 老师 " 中引用，因为
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: That's why on line four,
we can reference in anotherTeacher because
事实上有个蓝色的大理石叫做 " 老师"
there is in fact a blue
marble called anotherTeacher.
但是在 9 号线路上就没有老师了吧
But down on line nine,
there is no anotherTeacher, is there?
当我们在全球范围之外
When we're out in the global scope and
我们问你这个红色大理石的全球范围它会说不
we asked global scope you ever heard of
this red marble, it's gonna say nope,
从没听说过那个红色的大理石和我们要做什么参考错误
never heard of that red marble and what
we're gonna get there, reference error.
所以关键的区别，函数表达式，
So key difference, function expressions,
把你的范围确定为自己的范围
put there identify your
into their own scope.
有一点细微差别
There's a little nuance.
让我暂时回答这个问题。
Let me get to that question in a moment.
还有一点额外的细微差别不仅仅是蓝色的
There's a little, also, additional
nuance which is not only does that blue
云石出现在蓝色的范围内，但它也是只读的。
marble show up in the blue scope but
it's also read only.
您不能在第四行上重新分配 antherTeacher 。
You cannot reassign
anotherTeacher on line four.
您无法将其重新分配给某个其他值。
You could not reassign
it to some other value.
你有问题吗
You have a question, yes?
>> 演讲者 2: 为什么要这样做 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Why would you do this?
你为什么要在你的右边
Why would you actually have the named
function on the right side of
那个表情
that expression?
> > 演讲者 1: 你可能在那里更常看到它是一个匿名的功能
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: You've probably more often
seen it as an anonymous function there,
我们即将讨论所谓的所谓函数之间的区别
and we're about to discuss the difference
between what are so-called named function
表达式和更常见的匿名函数表达式。
expressions, and the more common
anonymous function expression.
好吧那我们一会儿就开始吧
Okay, so
we'll get into that in just a moment.
好的 segue，我们谈谈命名函数表达式。
So great segue, let's talk about
named function expressions.
什么是命名函数表达式?
What is a named function expression?
我们很有创意
We're super creative,
这意味着一个被赋予名字的函数表达式，好吗 ?
that means a function expression
that's been given a name, okay?
让我们看看这两个。
So let's look at these two.
第一条我要声明一个函数表达式
Line one,
I'm declaring a function expression.
为什么它是函数表达式?
Why is it a function expression?
>> 扬声器 2: 已分配给变量吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It's assigned to a variable?
>> 扬声器 1: 因为它不是函数声明，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: Because it's
not a function declaration,
我们怎么知道什么是功能声明
how do we know if something's
a function declaration
如果单词函数是语句中的第一个词吗 ?
if the word function is literally
the first thing in the statement?
所以如果这不是声明中的第一个问题的话
So if it's not the first thing in
the statement, if there's a variable or
一个运算符或括号什么的，那不是声明，是吗 ?
an operator or parentheses or anything,
then it's not a declaration, it is?
>> 扬声器 2: 表达式。 >> 扬声器 1: 表达式，因此
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: An expression.
&gt;&gt; Speaker 1: An expression, so
在第一行，我们看到一个函数表达式，但是我们没有看到任何名称。
on line one, we see a function expression,
but we see no name.
这叫做匿名函数表达式
So that's called a anonymous
function expression,
而第五行的则是命名函数表达式。
whereas the one on line five is
a named function expression.
因此，将函数表达式与
So setting aside the difference
between function expressions and
声明是暂时的
declarations for a moment.
在这里我只想把注意力集中到
Here, I just wanna focus our
attention to the difference between
匿名函数表达式和命名函数表达式。
anonymous function expressions and
named function expressions.
我想说的是尽管匿名的功能
And what I'm gonna claim is that
even though anonymous function
表达方式更普遍，更受欢迎，
expressions are vastly more common,
vastly more popular In fact,
大多数人甚至都没见过命名函数的表达方式
most of you have maybe never even
seen a named function expression.
这就是不寻常和不受欢迎的情况。
And that's how uncommon and
unpopular it is.
我要声明你应该永远的， 100%，零例外。
I'm going to make the claim that you
should always, 100%, zero exception.
我没有太多的陈述是绝对的 100%
I don't make very many statements
that are that absolute, 100%,
零异常，您应该更喜欢指定的函数表达式，
zero exceptions, you should prefer
the named function expression,
在匿名函数表达式中。
over the anonymous function expression.